<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Spotlight Demo</string>
    <string name="show_again">Show Again</string>
    <string name="spotlightIntroTitle">Spotlight? What Spotlight?</string>
    <string name="spotlightIntroDetail">It may be the name of the library, but the Spotlight is optional.
        There will be some Spotlights later, after these other features.</string>
    <string name="spotlightFluentTitle">Ease of Development</string>
    <string name="spotlightFluentDetail">A fluent interface simplifies producing Scripts with multiple
        Scenes:\n\n%s\n\nThe Script is the primary interface to the library. Adding Scenes to the Script adds new screens to the tutorial, and adding an Actor to a Scene will place a spotlight on the display.</string>
    <string name="spotlightTransitionsTitle">Support for Transitions</string>
    <string name="spotlightTransitionsDetail">A hard cut is the default transition, but a fade is also
        available. This Scene was presented with a two-second fade. The default duration for transitions is the system \"short\" animation duration.\n\nBecause transitions are associated with Scenes, a special empty Scene is used to control transition out of the last Scene. The SceneBuilder\'s end method will add this scene, if a transition is currently enabled.</string>
    <string name="spotlightDefaultsTitle">Defaults</string>
    <string name="spotlightDefaultsDetail">While most Scene properties are cleared for each new scene -
        for example, the fade used for the last scene is not repeated for this one - custom layouts and
        transitions also have setDefault methods that cause the following scenes to reuse a setting.
        \n\nThe next few Scenes will all use a short fade.</string>
    <string name="spotlightLayoutsTitle">Custom Text Layouts</string>
    <string name="spotlightLayoutsDetail">This Scene uses a custom text layout. Any layout that contains
        TextViews with the same IDs as in the default layout may be used. Custom layouts may be set for
        the Button and Spotlight as well - for these, the root of the layout must be of the correct type.</string>
    <string name="spotlightCollapseDetail">The title and detail text are both optional, and the default
        layout will collapse either if not present.</string>
    <string name="spotlightKittenTitle">Finally, A Spotlight!</string>
    <string name="spotlightKittenDetail">It\'s about time! The previous examples demonstrated most of the
        ways that Scenes can be customized, but didn\'t highlight anything. But look, here\'s a kitten!</string>
    <string name="spotlightAroundBaconTitle">Another Spotlight</string>
    <string name="spotlightAroundBaconDetail">This certainly is some meaty text. As with the kitten, the
        Actor for this Scene is a ViewActor with the default configuration, which circumscribes the selected View.
        The layout for this demo makes it a bit awkward in portrait mode.</string>
    <string name="spotlightActorConfigurationTitle">Spotlight Actor Configuration</string>
    <string name="spotlightActorConfigurationDetail">ViewActors can also be configured to inscribe the
        spotlight in the target instead of circumscribing the target. This may be more comfortable for
        very tall or wide Views.</string>
    <string name="spotlightSceneClearDefaultsTitle">Restoring Original Defaults</string>
    <string name="spotlightSceneClearDefaultsDetail">Scene properties for which defaults can be set also
        have matching clearDefault methods to restore the normal default behavior. The default transition
        was cleared before building this scene, restoring the original hard cut transition.</string>
    <string name="spotlightOneShotTitle">One-Shot Instructions</string>
    <string name="spotlightOneShotDetail">The other Scenes in this demo will only display once, but can
        be repeated by pressing the \"Show Again\" button.</string>
    <string name="aboutText">The <a href="https://github.com/Unhelpful/Spotlight">Spotlight Demo and Library</a> are Open Source Software.
        \n\nLicensed under the <a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">Apache License, Version 2.0</a>
        (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
        \n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
            distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
            WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
            See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
            limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
</resources>
